追溯到1835年 萨姆埃尔·柯尔特造了一把奇特的枪
Back in 1835, Samuel Colt made a special gun.
据说这把枪可以杀死任何东西
They say this gun can kill anything.
柯尔特已经死了 看起来那个恶魔很可能…
The Colt is gone and it seems pretty damn likely...
在背后操纵着一切
that the demon is behind all of this.
喂
Whoops.
十字路口是契约签订的地方 要出卖你的的灵魂
Crossroads are where pacts are made. Selling your soul.
仪式是这样的… 你要把你自己的照片埋进去 对吗？
Rituals like this. You put your photo in the mix, right?
我清楚你的一切 迪恩·温彻斯特
I know all about you, Dean Winchester.
我在寻找一个最棒的 最聪明的
I'm looking for the best and brightest.
- 我是萨姆 - 我是扎克
- I'm Sam. - I'm Jake.
这是一场竞赛
This is a competition.
你们这群疯狂的孩子之中 只有一个… 可以活着离开这里
Only one of you crazy kids is gonna make it out of here alive.
你坚强 你聪明
You are tough, smart.
你接受了很好的训练 萨姆 你是我的最爱
You're well trained, Sam. You're my favorite.
- 萨姆 - 迪恩
- Sam. - Dean.
萨姆 小心
Sam, look out.
不
No.
萨姆
Sam.
迪恩？
Dean?
带这个回来给你
Brought you this back.
不 谢谢 我很好
No, thanks. I'm fine.
你应该吃点东西
You should eat something.
我说了我很好
I said I'm fine.
迪恩
Dean.
我恨我提起这个 我真的恨
I hate to bring this up, I really do.
但你难道不认为我们 也许是时候…
But don't you think maybe it's time...
埋了萨姆吗？
we bury Sam?
不
No.
- 我们也许可以… - 什么 烧了尸体
- Well, we could maybe... - What, torch his corpse?
还不到时候
Not yet.
我要你跟我走
I want you to come with me.
我哪里也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
- 迪恩 拜托 - 你难道不能让我静一会儿
- Dean, please. - Would you cut me some slack?
我只是觉得你不应该一个人 仅此而已
I just don't think you should be alone, that's all.
我得承认 我需要你的帮助
I gotta admit I could use your help.
某些大事件要来了
Something big is going down.
- 如同世界末日般的 - 那就终结吧
- End-of-the-world big. - Well, then let it end!
你不会这样吧
You don't mean that.
你认为不会？
You don't think so?
你认为我得到的还不够多吗？
You don't think I've given enough?
你认为我付出的还不够多吗？
You don't think I've paid enough?
我受够了
I'm done with it.
所有的一切
All of it.
如果你知道怎样才好的话… 转身离开这里
If you knew what's good for you, turn around and get the hell out of here.
走
Go!
对不起
I'm sorry.
求你离开吧
Please, just go.
你知道我会在哪里
You know where I'll be.
[邪恶力量 第2季第22集]
你好 扎克
Howdy, Jake.
我… 我在做梦 对吧？
I-I'm dreaming, aren't I?
我手上有一个天才
I got a genius on my hands.
恭喜 扎克 你是…
Well, congratulations, Jake, you're it.
坚持到最后的人
Last man standing.
美国偶像
The American Idol.
我得承认 你不是我下注的那匹马 但是 我仍然会给你机会
I have to admit, you weren't the horse I was betting on but still, I gotta give it to you.
见鬼去吧
Go to hell.
去过了 见过了
Been there. Done that.
你把我卷入的这一切…
Everything you put me through.
把我弄到那个地方 让我杀了那些人
Dragging me to that place, making me kill those people.
都是"选美比赛"的一部分
All part of the beauty pageant.
扎克 我需要一个最强的人
Jake, I needed the strongest.
那就是你
And that's you.
需要我做什么？
Needed me for what?
我有一大张刺激的清单给你
Oh, I got a laundry list of tasty things for you.
我要做的唯一的事… 就是醒过来
The only thing I'm gonna do, is wake up...
击倒你 然后亲手杀了你
hunt you down and kill you myself.
你知道吗 其他人试过了
You know, others have tried.
不容易
It's not easy.
相信我 扎克 你想成为一个很棒的小兵
Trust me, Jake, you wanna be a good little soldier here.
如果我不想呢？
And if I'm not?
如果你是个坏小兵
If you're a bad little soldier?
你那亲爱的老母亲…
Well, that dear old mom of yours...
那可爱的小妹妹…
that adorable little sister?
我保证他们都能活的足够长来…
I'll make certain that they both live long enough...
了解他们自己内脏的嚼劲
to know the chewy taste of their own intestines.
不 扎克 我没有胡说
No, Jake, I'm not bluffing.
你要我做什么？
What do you want me to do?
像我说的 天赋
Like I said. Genius.
你知道 在我们小时候…
You know, when we were little...
你5岁还没到…
and you couldn't have been more than 5...
你就开始提问题
you just started asking questions.
我们怎么没有妈妈？
How come we didn't have a mom?
为什么我们总是搬家？
Why do we always have to move around?
他去哪儿了？
Where'd Dad go?
离开一段时间的时候
He'd take off for days at a time.
我记得我求你说 别再问了 萨姆
I remember I begged you, "Quit asking, Sammy.
伙计 你不会想知道的
Man, you don't wanna know."
我只想让你当一个孩子
I just wanted you to be a kid.
就再当久一点
Just for a little while longer.
我一直试着保护你
I always tried to protect you.
保障你的安全
Keep you safe.
爸爸甚至没有告诉我
Dad didn't even have to tell me.
这永远是我的职责 你知道吗？
It was just always my responsibility, you know?
就像我一个任务
It's like I had one job.
我有一个任务…
That one job.
而我搞砸了
And I screwed it up.
我吹牛了
I blew it.
为了这个 对不起
And for that, I'm sorry.
我猜我就是这样的…
I guess that's what I do.
我让我所爱的人失望
I let down the people I love.
我令爸爸失望
I let Dad down.
现在我猜可能也要让你失望了
And now, I guess I'm just supposed to let you down too?
我怎么能？
How can I?
这样我怎么能活的下去？
How am I supposed to live with that?
我该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
萨姆
Sammy.
我该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
快点 已经好了
Oh, come on already.
露出你的脸 你这个婊子
Show your face, you bitch.
放松点 甜心 你会吵醒邻居的
Easy, sugar, you'll wake the neighbors.
迪恩
Dean.
见到你真是太棒了
It is so, so good to see you.
我是说真的 看看你
I mean it. Look at you.
令你的家人都死了 孤单的活在世上
Gone and got your family killed. All alone in the world.
这太美妙了
It's too sweet.
不好意思 你得让我离开下
Excuse me, you're gonna have to give me a moment.
有时候你得停下来 闻闻玫瑰的花香
Sometimes you gotta stop and smell the roses.
我应该把你直接送回地狱
I should send you straight back to hell.
你应该 但你不会
Oh, you should. But you won't.
我知道为什么
And I know why.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
追随父亲的脚步 你想做笔交易
Following in Daddy's footsteps. You wanna make a deal.
小萨姆的起死回生
Little Sammy, back from the dead.
让我猜猜 出卖你自己的灵魂？
And let me guess, you're offering up your own soul?
还有数百个其他的… 想要出手的恶魔
There are a hundred other demons who'd love to get their hands on it.
这都取决于你 你所要做的就是带萨姆回来
And it's all yours. All you gotta do is bring Sam back.
给我10年时间
You give me 10 years.
10年 然后你就来拿我
Ten years and then you come for me.
你一定是在开玩笑
You must be joking.
那是与你给其他人 一样的条件
It's the same deal you give everybody else.
你不是其他人
You're not everybody else.
我为什么要给你任何东西？
Why would I wanna give you anything?
留着你的破灵魂吧 总之 是太残败了
Keep your gutter soul, it's too tarnished anyway.
- 9年 - 不
- Nine years. - No.
- 8年 - 你继续 我会一直说不
- Eight. - You keep going, I'll keep saying no.
好吧 5年
Okay, five years.
5年后 我的帐到期
Five years, then my bill comes due.
这是我最后的出价 5年否则就没交易
That's my last offer. Five years or no deal.
那么就没交易
Then no deal.
- 好 - 好
- Fine. - Fine.
确保在萨姆腐烂之前 把他埋掉
Make sure you bury Sam before he starts stinking up the joint.
等等
Wait.
这是大特价 所有东西必须出手
It's a fire sale and everything must go.
我要做什么？
What do I have to do?
首先 别卑躬屈节的 低三下四的男人很倒胃口
First of all, quit groveling. Needy guys are such a turnoff.
瞧…
Look.
我不应该这样做 我会陷入很多麻烦之中
Look, I shouldn't be doing this. I could get in a lot of trouble.
但是我能说什么？我对你没办法 迪恩
But what can I say? I got a blind spot for you, Dean.
你就像个… 小狗崽 和你玩真是太有趣了
You're like a puppy, you're just too fun to play with.
我会做的
I'll do it.
- 你会带他回来吗 - 我会的
- You'll bring him back? - I will.
因为我是如此一个好人 我会给你一年时间 只有一年
And because I'm just such a saint, I'll give you one year and one year only.
但是重点是…
But here's the thing.
如果你试图逃避或者躲藏的话… 那么交易就结束
If you try and welch or weasel your way out, then the deal is off.
萨姆就会死… 他立即就会变回腐烂的臭肉
Sam drops dead, he's back to rotten meat in no time.
那么…
So?
比你爸爸做的交易更好
It's a better deal than your Dad ever got.
你认为呢？
What do you say?
萨弥
Sammy?
感谢上帝
- Thank God. - Hey.
呃… 迪恩…
Uh, Dean.
对不起 对不起 伙计 我只是…
Sorry. I'm sorry, man, I'm just...
我只是见到你起来太高兴了 就是这样
I'm happy to see you up and around, that's all.
- 来 坐下 - 好
- Come on, sit down. - Okay.
迪恩 我怎么了？
Dean, what happened to me?
你记得什么？
Well, what do you remember?
我… 我看到你和博比
I-I saw you and Bobby and...
我感觉到疼痛 这种极度的疼痛就像… 就像 极端的 你知道的
Then I felt this pain. This sharp pain, like white hot, you know.
然后… 然后你跑向我… 就这些
And then you started running at me and that's about it.
是的 那… 那个小子 从背后刺伤了你
Yeah, that kid stabbed you in the back.
你失了很多血 很严重而且持续了很久
You lost a lot of blood. You know, it was pretty touch and go for a while.
但是迪恩 你… 你不可能 治疗那么严重的伤口
But, Dean, you can't patch up a wound that bad.
是的 博比能
No, Bobby could.
- 不管如何 那个小子是谁 - 他的名字是扎克
- Who was that kid anyway? - His name's Jake.
- 你抓到他了吗 - 没有 他消失在树林中了
- Did you get him? - No. He disappeared in the woods.
我们得找到他 迪恩
We gotta find him, Dean.
而且我发誓 要把那个狗杂种撕成碎片
And I swear, I'm gonna tear that son of a bitch apart.
放松点 范·达姆
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, Van Damme.
你刚刚醒过来 好吗？我们吃点东西
You just woke up. Let's get you something to eat. Huh?
你想吃点东西吗？
You want something to eat?
我饿死了 来吧
I'm starving. Come on.
然后你们就出现了
And that's when you guys showed up.
那太可怕了
That's awful.
可怜的安迪
Poor Andy.
恶魔说他只想让 我们中的一个或者走出去
Demon said he only wanted one of us to walk out alive.
- 他告诉你的 - 是的
- And he told you that? - Yup.
- 他出现在梦中 - 他告诉你其他什么吗？
- Appeared in a dream. - He tell you anything else?
不 没有 就那些 没其他的
No. No, that was it, nothing else.
你知道吗 我不明白的是 迪恩 如果恶魔只想要我们中的一个
You know, what I don't get, Dean, is if the demon only wanted one of us...
那么为何我和扎克都能离开？
then how did Jake and I both get away?
我是说 他们留你等死 我肯定他们以为结束了
Well, I mean, they left you for dead. I'm sure they thought it was over.
现在那个黄眼有扎克了 他会对他怎么样？
Now that Yellow Eyes has Jake, what's he gonna do with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是无论是什么 我们得阻止他
But whatever it is, we gotta stop it.
等等 好吗？ 你需要休息
Well, hold on, all right? You need to get your rest.
- 我们有时间 - 不 我们没有
- We got time. - No, we don't.
萨姆 大海还没沸腾呢 好吗？
Sam, oceans aren't boiling, okay?
雾不是从天上落下来的 我们要先让你恢复体力
Frogs aren't raining from the sky. Let's get you your strength back first.
你问过路边旅馆了吗？他们知道什么吗？
Well, did you call the Roadhouse? They know anything?
是的
Yeah.
迪恩… 怎么了？
Dean, what is it?
路边旅馆被烧平了
The Roadhouse burned to the ground.
阿什死了
Ash is dead.
艾伦也许… 也有很多其他的猎人
Probably, Ellen, a lot of other hunters too.
- 恶魔 - 是 我们认为是的
- Demons? - Yeah, we think so.
- 我们认为原因是阿什发现了些什么 - 他发现了什么？
- We think because Ash found something. - What did he find?
博比正在调查
Bobby's working on that right now.
那么 走吧 博比离我们就几个小时的路
Well, come on then. Bobby's only a few hours away.
停下 萨姆 停 该死的
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop, Sam, stop. Damn it.
你差一点就死在… 我是说 我要…
You almost died in there. I mean, what would I have-?
你就更好的照顾好自己 就更好一点
Can't you just take care of yourself for a little bit, huh? Just for a little bit.
对不起 不
I'm sorry. No.
- 嗨 博比 - 嗨 博比
- Hey, Bobby. - Hey, Bobby.
萨姆
Sam.
见到你
It's good to...
又站起来了… 真好
see you up and around.
是的…
Yeah.
谢谢你救活我
Well, thanks for patching me up.
别客气
Don't mention it.
萨姆好点了
Well, Sam's better.
我们现在回来了
And we're back in it now.
那么… 你了解到什么了？
So, what do you know?
我找到些东西
Well, I found something.
但是我不确定到底是什么意思
But I'm not sure what the hell it means.
是什么？
What is it?
恶魔的征兆…
Demonic omens.
就像该死的 涨潮落潮
Like a frigging tidal wave.
牲畜死亡 电闪雷鸣
Cattle deaths, lightning storms.
凭空出现
They've skyrocketed from out of nowhere.
这里
Here.
都在这周围
All around here.
除了一个地方以外…
Except for one place.
- 南怀俄明州 - 怀俄明州？
- Southern Wyoming. - Wyoming?
是的 那个地区完全干净 无际可寻
Yeah, that one area's totally clean. Spotless.
- 基本就像… - 什么
- It's almost as if... - What?
恶魔在包围那儿
the demons are surrounding it.
但你知道为什么吗？
You don't know why?
不 目前为止 我毫无头绪
No, and by this point my eyes are swimming.
萨姆 你能看看吗？也许你能发现些 我发现不了的东西
Would you take a look at it? Maybe you can catch something I couldn't.
好 当然
Yeah. Sure.
来吧 迪恩 卡车里还有更多的书…
Come on, Dean. I got some more books in the truck.
帮我拖进来
Help me lug them in.
好
Yeah.
你这个白痴傻蛋 你做了什么
You stupid ass. What did you do?
你做了什么
What did you do?
你做了笔交易… 为了萨姆 是不是
You made a deal. For Sam, didn't you?
- 他们给你多久 - 博比
- How long they give you? - Bobby.
多久
How long?
一年
One year.
该死的 迪恩
Damn it, Dean.
这就是我们为什么 要找到那个黄眼狗杂种
Which is why we gotta find this yellow-eyed son of a bitch.
那就是为什么我要亲手杀了他 我现在没有什么 可以输的了 对吧
That's why I'm gonna kill him myself. I mean, I got nothing to lose now, right?
我真想杀了你
I could throttle you.
提前把我送到下面去？
And send me downstairs ahead of schedule?
你们姓温彻斯特都怎么了 恩
What is it with you Winchesters, huh?
你 你爸爸 你们都渴望把自己送到地狱去
You, your dad, you're both just itching to throw yourselves down the pit.
这就是我的问题
That's my point.
爸爸把我带回来的 博比 我甚至都不该在这里
Dad brought me back, Bobby, I'm not even supposed to be here.
至少这样… 才能更加有意义 你知道吗？
At least this way, something good can come out of it, you know.
像是我的生命能更有意义
Like my life can mean something.
什么 之前没有吗？
What, and it didn't before?
你对你自己 有这么低劣的评价吗？
Have you got that low an opinion of yourself?
你是那么白痴吗
Are you that screwed in the head?
我不能让他死 博比
I couldn't let him die, Bobby.
我不能
I couldn't.
他是我的兄弟
He's my brother.
你的兄弟会怎么想… 当他知道你会下地狱？
How is your brother gonna feel when he knows you're going to hell?
当你知道你爸爸为了你 这么做的时候你什么感觉
How'd you feel when you knew your dad went for you?
你不能告诉他
You can't tell him.
你开枪打死我 无论你做什么… 但是拜托不要告诉他
You take a shot at me, whatever you gotta do. But please don't tell him.
艾伦？
Ellen?
艾伦 哦 上帝啊
Ellen. Oh, God.
博比 这真的需要吗？
Bobby, is this really necessary?
只是一杯圣水 不会伤害你的
Just a belt of holy water. Shouldn't hurt.
现在 威士忌吧 如果你不介意的话
Whiskey now, if you don't mind.
- 艾伦 发生什么了 - 你怎么逃出来的？
- Ellen, what happened? How'd you get out? - I wasn't supposed to.
我本不该的 我本该和其他人一起在那儿的
I was supposed to be in there with everybody else.
但是我们去买椒盐卷饼了
But we ran out of pretzels, of all things.
只是该死的运气
Was just dumb luck.
总之 那时候阿什打过电话 声音很惊恐
Anyway, that's when Ash called, panic in his voice.
他告诉我去看一下保险箱 然后电话就断了
He told me to look in the safe. Then the call cut out.
当我回去的时候 已是漫天大火
By the time I got back, the flames were sky high.
所有人都死了 我离开不过15分钟
Everybody was dead. I couldn't have been gone more than 15 minutes.
对不起 艾伦
Sorry, Ellen.
许多好人死在了那里
Lot of good people died in there.
而我活了下来
And I got to live.
幸运的我
Lucky me.
艾伦 你提到一个保险箱
Ellen, you mentioned a safe.
一个我们保存在 地下室的隐蔽保险箱
A hidden safe we keep in the basement.
恶魔拿到里面的东西了吗
Demons get what was in it?
没有
No.
怀俄明州
Wyoming?
那是什么意思？
What does that mean?
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
什么 你找到什么了吗
What, you got something?
不止一点儿
A lot more than that.
每一个X代表一个 被废弃的边境教堂 都是19世纪中期的
Each of these X's is an abandoned frontier church, all mid-19th century.
全都是萨姆埃尔·柯尔特建造的
And all of them built by Samuel Colt.
萨姆埃尔·柯尔特 那个造猎鬼枪的萨姆埃尔·柯尔特？
Samuel Colt? The demon-killing, gun-making Samuel Colt?
是的
Yep.
还有更多
And there's more.
他在教堂间建造了 互相连接的私人铁路
He built private railway lines connecting church to church.
恰好就形成了这个
That just happens to lay out like this.
- 告诉我这不是我想的那样 - 那是一个恶魔之束缚
- Tell me that's not what I think it is. - It's a Devil's Trap.
- 一个100平方英里的恶魔之束缚 - 太有才了
- A hundred-square-mile Devil's Trap. - That's brilliant.
恶魔无法跨越铁路线
Iron lines, demons can't cross.
- 我从没听说过如此宏伟的东西 - 没有人听过
- I never heard of anything that massive. - No one has.
这么多年没有一条线路损坏吗 它还在工作
All these years none of the lines are broken? I mean, it still works?
那是肯定的
Definitely.
- 你怎么知道的 - 所有那些博比找到的前兆
- How do you know? - All those omens Bobby found.
那些恶魔 他们肯定游荡在周围 但是却进不去
I mean, the demons, they must be circling and they can't get in.
- 是啊 他们在尝试 - 为什么 那里面有什么
- Yeah, well, they're trying. - Why? What's inside?
那就是我一直在调查的 然后…
That's what I've been looking for. And, uh, there's nothing...
里面除了正中间的 一个古老的牛仔公墓以外… 其他什么都没有
except an old cowboy cemetery right in the middle.
好吧 一个公墓 有什么如此重要？
Why? What's so important about a cemetery?
柯尔特在保护些什么？
What's Colt trying to protect?
- 好吧 除非… - 除非什么
- Well, unless... - Unless what?
如果柯尔特并不是尝试 要把恶魔们关在外面呢？
What if Colt wasn't trying to keep demons out?
如果他只是要把 某些东西关在里面呢？
What if he was keeping something in?
- 令人鼓舞的想法 - 是啊 你认为呢？
- Now, that's a comforting thought. - Yeah, you think?
- 他们能做到吗博比 他们能进去吗 - 这东西太强大了
- Could they do it? Could they get inside? - This thing's so powerful...
你几乎需要一个原子弹 才能摧毁他们
you'd practically need an A-bomb to destroy it.
纯种恶魔想要穿越进去 绝对没门儿
No way a full-blood demon gets across.
不
No.
但是我知道谁可以
But I know who could.
你好 扎克
Howdy, Jake.
那么 一路上愉快吗？
So did you have a nice trip?
我来了 我做了你叫我做的 现在怎样
I'm here. I did what you asked. Now what?
那条路过去50英里
Fifty miles, thataway.
那有一个公墓 一个地窖 你要为我打开它
There's a cemetery, a crypt. You gotta open that for me.
你觉得你能做到吗？
Think you can manage that, sport?
知道吗 你和你那变态的命令见鬼去吧 你自己去做
You know what? Screw you and your freaky orders. Go do it yourself.
哦 我不能 我不能过去
Oh, I can't. I can't go that way.
- 还不能 - 为什么不能？
- Not yet. - Why not?
我就是不能
I just can't.
但是如果你 为我打开那个地窖 你将会需要一把钥匙
But if you're gonna open that crypt for me, you're gonna need a key.
- 一把枪 - 哦 这可不仅仅是一把枪 扎克
- A gun? - Oh, this isn't just any gun, Jake.
这是这宇宙中唯一的一把… 能够杀掉我的枪
This is the only gun in the whole universe that can shoot me dead.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Is that so? - Yep.
这儿 拿着
Here, take it.
哦 我的… 我对这无法预料的转折 还真惊讶
Oh, my...I'm shocked at this unforeseen turn of events.
来吧 扎克 扣下扳机吧 尽你所能
Go ahead, Jake. Squeeze that trigger. Be all you can be.
这一切都会结束 你的生活都会恢复正常
This'll all be over. Your life can go back to normal.
当然了 因为你的擅离职守 军队也不会再要你
Course, the Army won't take you back because you're AWOL.
但是我肯定你能在工厂里 找回你的旧工作
But I'm sure you could get your old job at the factory back.
但是然后 从另一方面来说… 你和你家人剩下的日子
But then on the other hand, the rest of your life and your family's...
会是富有 甜蜜 健康 富足
could be money and honey, health and wealth.
每一天都是像冰淇淋一般甜蜜
Every day is ice cream Sunday.
而你所需要做的只是 那么一点点小事
And all you gotta do is this one little thing.
- 为什么是我 - 哦 扎克 一定要是你
- Why me? - Oh, Jake, it's gotta be you.
我等你已经等了很久了
I've been waiting for you for a very long time.
你是我的首领 你打开那个地窖 你就会得到你的军队
You're my leader. You open that crypt and you will have your army.
- 你在说的是世界末日吗 - 不 不是末日
- You're talking about the end of the world. - No, not the end.
而是开始… 一个更好的世界
The beginning. A better world.
那里你的家庭会被保护起来
Where your family will be protected.
还有更多
More than that.
他们会是皇室
They'll be royalty.
小伙子 你有了一个
Buddy boy, you'll have the chance to get in...
如此令人激动的好机会
on the ground floor of a thrilling opportunity.
你怎么说 由你自己决定
What do you say? It's your call.
乖孩子
Attababy.
你好 扎克
Howdy, Jake.
等等…
Oh, you.
你已经死了 我杀了你
You were dead. I killed you.
是吗？
Yeah?
那么 下一次完成任务
Well, next time finish the job.
我有
I did.
我完全割断了你的脊髓
I cut clean through your spinal cord, man.
你不可能还活着
You can't be alive.
- 不可能 - 好了 好好冷静下来 孩子
- You can't be. - Okay. Just take it real easy there, son.
- 如果我不呢 - 走着瞧
- And if I don't? - Wait and see.
怎么 突然就变成男子汉了 你想怎么做
What, you a tough guy all of a sudden? What are you gonna do?
- 杀了我 - 是有这想法
- Kill me? - It's a thought.
你有过机会的 但是你没能做到
You had your chance. You couldn't.
同样的错误我不会犯两次
I won't make that mistake twice.
在笑什么呢 你这小贱人
What are you smiling at, you little bitch?
嘿 女士
Hey, lady.
帮我做件事儿
Do me a favor.
把枪指着你自己的脑袋
Put that gun to your head.
看吧 那个女孩艾娃是对的
See, that Ava girl was right.
一旦你投入进去 有好多种摄心术能学
Once you give into it, there's all sorts of new Jedi Mind Tricks you can learn.
- 让她走 - 射他
- Let her go. - Shoot him.
在你们开枪之前 可要弹掉你们身上她的头骨的
You'll be mopping up skull before you get a shot off.
所有人 把枪放下
Everybody put your guns down.
除了你 甜心
Except you, sweetheart.
好了 谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
求你
Please.
不要
No.
求你
Please-
- 哦 不 - 博比 这是什么？
- Oh, no. - Bobby, what is it?
是地狱
It's hell.
藏起来 快
Take cover. Now.
- 刚刚到底发生了什么 - 那是恶魔之门 该死的地狱之门
- What the hell just happened? - That's a Devil's Gate, a damn door to hell.
来吧 我们去关上那个门
Come on, we gotta shut that gate.
如果恶魔给了扎克这个…
If the demon gave this to Jake...
那么也许…
then maybe...
小孩子不该玩爸爸的枪
Boys shouldn't play with Daddy's guns.
迪恩
Dean.
我一会儿再来处理你 性急的家伙 我为你骄傲
I'll get to you in a minute, champ. But I'm proud of you.
知道你很有种
I knew you had it in you.
坐下的咒符
Sit a spell.
那么 迪恩… 我得感谢你
So, Dean, I gotta thank you.
如果没有交易 恶魔无法复活人
You see, demons can't resurrect people unless a deal is made.
我知道 很艰难 让你很白痴
I know, red tape, it'll make you nuts.
但是托你的福 萨姆又回来了
But thanks to you, Sammy's back in rotation. Ha, ha.
我没有指望那个 但我很高兴
Now, I wasn't counting on that but I'm glad.
比起扎克我更喜欢萨姆
I liked him better than Jake anyhow.
告诉我 你有没有听到这句话…
Tell me, you ever heard the expression:
"如果一笔交易太棒了以至于 无法相信 可能那就是真的"
"If a deal sounds too good to be true, it probably is"?
你称这为好的交易？
You call that deal good?
比你父亲的那个要好
Ah, it's a better shake than your Dad ever got.
你知道为什么吗？
And you never wondered why.
我为你感到惊讶
I'm surprised at you.
我的意思是… 你看见你弟弟对扎克 做了什么 对吧？
I mean, you saw what your brother just did to Jake, right?
那还挺无情的 不是吗？
That was pretty cold, wasn't it?
你有多确定…
How certain are you that what you brought back...
你带回来的是100%的萨姆
is 100 percent pure Sam?
在你经历过的一切之后
After everything you've been through.
你所有的…
Everything you've...
你们人都知道 死了就是死了
You of all people should know that what's dead should stay dead.
总之…
Anyway...
谢谢你朋友
thanks a bunch.
我知道我让你活着是有原因的
I knew I kept you alive for some reason.
总之 直到现在
Until now anyway.
我是不会成功的如果… 没有你可悲的自卑…
I couldn't have done it without your pathetic self-loathing...
自我毁灭倾向… 为你的家庭牺牲自己
self-destructive desire to sacrifice yourself for your family.
任务总算完成了
Well, check that off the to do list.
- 你做到了 - 我不是一个人做到的
- You did it. - I didn't do it alone.
你认为爸爸真的…
Do you think Dad really...
你认为他真的是 从地狱爬上来的吗？
You think he really climbed out of hell?
之前门开了
A door was open.
如果谁会如此顽固的话…
If anyone's stubborn enough to do it...
那就一定是他
it'd be him.
你认为他现在会在哪儿？
Where do you think he is now?
我不知道
I don't know.
我有点不敢相信 迪恩 我的意思是…
I kind of can't believe it, Dean. I mean...
我们的一生 所有的一切… 都为了这一刻…
Our whole lives, everything, has been prepping for this. And now, I...
我有些不知道该说些什么
I kind of don't know what to say.
我知道
I do.
这是为了我们的母亲…
That was for our mom.
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
你知道 当扎克看到我的时候… 就像看到了鬼一样
You know, when Jake saw me it was like he saw a ghost.
我是说 见鬼的 我听见他说的了 迪恩
I mean, hell, you heard him, Dean.
他说他杀了我
He said he killed me.
很高兴他说错了
Glad he was wrong.
我认为他没有 迪恩
I don't think he was, Dean.
当我被刺了以后发生了什么？
What happened?After I was stabbed?
- 我已经告诉你了 - 不是每件事
- I already told you. - Not everything.
萨姆 我们刚杀了一个魔鬼
Sam, we just killed the demon.
我们能庆祝一下吗？
Can we celebrate for a minute?
我死了吗？
Did I die?
拜托
Oh, come on.
你出卖了自己的灵魂来救我 就像爸爸为你做的一样？
Did you sell your soul for me? Like Dad did for you?
拜托 没有
Come on. No.
告诉我真相
Tell me the truth.
- 迪恩 告诉我真相 - 萨姆…
- Dean, tell me the truth. - Sam.
你有多久？
How long you get?
1年
One year.
我有1年
I got one year.
你不该这么做的
You shouldn't have done that.
- 你怎么能这样做呢 - 别生我的气
- How could you do that? - Don't get mad at me.
别这么做
Don't you do that.
我必须这么做
I had to.
我必须得照顾你
I had to look out for you.
- 那是我的工作 - 你认为我的工作是什么？
- That's my job. - And what do you think my job is?
- 什么 - 你一次又一次的救我
- What? - You saved my life over and over.
你牺牲了一切来救我 你难道不认为 我也会为你这样做吗？
I mean, you sacrifice everything for me. Don't you think I'd do the same for you?
你是我的大哥
You're my big brother.
没有任何事我不会为你做
There's nothing I wouldn't do for you.
我不管代价是什么 我要把你救回来
And I don't care what it takes. I'm gonna get you out of this.
我猜这次我要救你了
Guess I gotta save your ass for a change.
是啊
Yeah.
那么
Well...
黄眼也许已经死了 但却有很多穿过了那门
Yellow-Eyed Demon might be dead but a lot more got through that gate.
你认为有多少？
How many you think?
一百
A hundred.
也许200 是一支军队
Maybe 200. It's an army.
他释放了一支军队
He's unleashed an army.
希望你们已经准备好了
Hope to hell you boys are ready.
因为战争才刚刚开始
Because the war's just begun.
那么…
Well, then...
我们有活儿干了
we got work to do.